covering the week's top tech stores it's
pokrivajući sedmice vrhunskih prodavaonica
like Linux bias Apple has begun selling
poput Linux pristranosti Apple je počeo prodavati
the rack-mountable variant of its Mac
varijanta Maca koji se može montirati na stalak
Pro desktop computer starting at just
Pro stolni računar koji počinje od samog trenutka
6500 dollars the rack-mounted Mac Pro is
6500 dolara košta Mac Pro
identical to the tower version in terms
u terminima identičan verziji kule
of specifications and it comes in the
specifikacija i dolazi u
same hardware configurations as well it
iste hardverske konfiguracije
has the same ports it's laid out the
ima iste portove na kojima je postavljen
same inside the case and it has the same
isto unutar kućišta i ima isto
rear connections the differences from
stražnje spojeve razlike od
the tower variant are entirely in the
varijanta tornja je u potpunosti u
case itself this variant of the Mac Pro
sama varijanta Maca Pro
forgoes the wheels or stands of the
odustaje od kotača ili postolja
tower model in favor of stainless steel
model tornja u korist nehrđajućeg čelika
rails that allow the device to be
šine koje omogućuju uređaj
mounted horizontally in server racks it
ugrađen vodoravno u ležište poslužitelja
also has a removable lid instead of the
takođe ima uklonjivi poklopac umesto
fully removable frame seen in the tower
potpuno uklonjivi okvir viđen u tornju
additionally the handles are on the
dodatno su ručke na
front for easy removal from server racks
prednja strana za lako uklanjanje sa serverskih regala
and some other elements like the power
i neki drugi elementi poput snage
button have been moved from the tower
dugme je pomereno sa tornja
top to the front rack this Mac Pro is
vrh prednjeg nosača koji je ovaj Mac Pro
intended for inclusion in render farms
namijenjeno uključivanju u uzgajališta
as a server and other commercial and
kao server i ostali komercijalni i
professional uses I could certainly see
profesionalnu upotrebu koju bih sigurno mogao vidjeti
in the render farm I mean I work in
na renderiranoj farmi mislim da radim
video all the time so having something
neprestano video tako da ima nešto
that's able to do my rendering that's
to može da uradi moje prikazanje to
that powerful but does it have to be a
tako moćan, ali mora da bude
Mac could it be ill the next machine
Mac bi mogao biti bolestan naredna mašina
with blender running that would be sweet
s blenderom koji bi bio sladak
let's go
Idemo
[Music]
[Muzika]